A Guide to the University of Virginia Office of the Vice President for Business and Finance Office Administrative Files, 1909, [1953]-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Office of the Vice President for Business and Finance Office Administrative Files 1909, [1953]-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-5/1/1.831
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student and employee records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.) and the Freedom of Information Act (F.O.I.A.). In addition, the collection may contain confidential donor information.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from the Office of the Vice President, 1983 December 16.
Scope and Content
The records consist of correspondence files of the Vice President for Business and Finance and Chief Operating Officer and include an alphabetical file for each biennium, along with separate files the Auditor of Public Accounts, Business and Auxiliary services and State office files.
Contents List
- Vice-President for Business and Finance 1975-1976
  - Admissions, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Board of Trustees, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1975-1976, 2 folders. (Box 1)
  - Arboretum Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Art, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Associate Provost for Research, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Athletics, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors Finance Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors Health Sciences Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Budget, Biennium, 1976-1978 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, Carr's Hill Road, 1967-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, CVC-Administration and Classroom Building, 1968-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, CVC-Boys' Dormitory, 1967-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, CVC-Library, 1965-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, CVC-Maintenance Building, 1968-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, CVC-Women's Dormitory, 1966-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, Health Sciences Library, 1965-1976, 2 folders. (Box 1)
  - Building Program, Lambeth Field Access Road, 1972-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, Married Student Housing, Phase II, 1969-1973 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, Nursing School Building, 1967-1976 (Box 1)
  - Building Program, Physics Building, 1965-1976 (Box 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Maintenance, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Bursar, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Business Manager, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Center for Advanced Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Charlottesville, City of, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Clinch Valley College, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate School of Business Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - College, Dean of, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Comptroller for Medical Affairs, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Continuing Education, School of, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Council of President, State Council of Higher Education, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Council of State Senior Business Officers, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Counsellor to the President for Special Development, 1972-1976 (Box 2)
  - Counsellor to the President for Special Development, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Darden, C.W., Jr., 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Deans, Academic, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Division of Personnel, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Division of the Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Education, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Endowment Funds (Consolidated), 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Endowment Funds (Eminent Scholars), 1971-1976 (Box 2)
  - Energy Conservation Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Engineering, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Executive Vice-President, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs, Office of, 1971-1976 (Box 2)
  - Equal Opportunities Programs, Office of, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Food Services, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Food Services Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 2)
  - University of Virginia Alumni Association, n.d. (Box 2)
  - The Lawn Society, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Law School Alumni Association, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Medical Alumni Association at the University of Virginia, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Alumnae Association of the University of Virginia School of Nursing, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Engineering Foundation, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Fund Raising Group, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Governor, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Graduate Studies, Dean of, 1965-1976 (Box 2)
  - Health Sciences, Vice-President for, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - History, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Hospital, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Housing Office, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Institute of Government, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Internal Audit Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Law, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advisor, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Library, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - McIntire School of Commerce, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Madison House, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Medical Center, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Medicine, School of, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Miller, Burkett Center for Public Affairs, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Mortgage Loans, Approved Applications, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Mortgage Loans, Faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - NACUBO, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Nursing, School of, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Parking and Transit, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Personnel Office, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Physics, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - President, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Provost, 1971-1976 (Box 3)
  - Resource Recovery Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Retirement Plans, VSRS and TIAA, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - RLES, 1973-1976 (Box 3)
  - SACUBO, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Safety and Security Department, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Space Administrator, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Student Affairs, Vice-President for, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Summer Quarter, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Treasurer, 1972-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Comptroller, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Development, Director of, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Police Department, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Press, 1965-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Development Steering Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 3)
- Vice-President for Business and Finance, 1976-1977
  - Admissions, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Board of Trustees, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1977, 2 folders. (Box 3)
  - Arboretum Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Architecture, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Assistant Comptroller, 1973, 1976-77 (Box 3)
  - Associate Provost for Research, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Athletics, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Blandy Farm, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors, 1975-1978 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors, Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors, Finance Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors, Health Sciences Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Budget Director, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds Monthly Reports, 1976 July- 1977 May, 4 folders. (Box 3)
  - Business Manager, 1974, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Calender and Scheduling Committee, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Clinch Valley College, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate School of Business Administration, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments: Art 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments: Economics 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments: Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Dean of, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments: Government and Foreign Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments: Music, 1975 (Box 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments: Service Physical Education, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Colonnade Club Annex, 1967, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
  - Comptroller, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Comptroller for Medical Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Computing Activities, Region II 1974, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Concert Series, 1953-1977 (Box 4)
  - Council of President, State Council of Higher Education, 1972, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Council of State Senior Business Officers, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Development, Vice-President for, 1971, 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Division of Personnel, 1972-1974, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Division of the Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - EACUBO, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Education, State Department of, 1971, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Endowed Chairs, (Second and Third Chairs Dinners), 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Endowment Funds (Eminent Scholars, Investment of), 1974-1976 (Box 4)
  - Endowment Funds, (Consolidated), 1977, 1976, 2 folders. (Box 4)
  - Endowment Funds (Eminent Scholars), 1964-1977 (Box 4)
  - Executive Vice-President, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Salaries [American Association of University Professors], 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - Federal Executive Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Financial Aid to Students, Office of, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Food Service Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 4)
  - Fund Raising Group, 1975 (Box 4)
  - General Assembly, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Governor, 1970, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Health Sciences, Vice-President, 1971, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Highways and Transportation, Department of, 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - Housing Office, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Institutional Analysis Office, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Law, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Lawn Crosswalks, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Lawn Railings, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
  - Legal Advisor, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Library, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - McIntire School of Commerce, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Madison House, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Medical Alumni Association, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Medical Center, 1966, 1974-1977 (Box 4)
  - Medicine, School of, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Miller, Burkett Center for Public Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - James Monroe Memorial Foundation, 1964-1972 (Box 4)
  - Mortgage Loans, Approved Applications, 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Mortgage Loans, Faculty, 1962-1976 (Box 4)
  - Parking and Transit, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Personnel Office, 1972-1977 (Box 4)
  - Planning, Department of, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - President, 1971-1977 (Box 4)
  - Property- Miscellaneous, 1961-1967, 1968-1971, 2 folders. (Box 4)
  - Provost, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Public Affairs Center, 1967, 1971, 3 folders. (Box 5)
  - RLES, 1976 January-June (Box 5)
  - Registrar, 1972-1977 (Box 5)
  - Resource Recovery Committee, 1975 February (Box 5)
  - Safety and Security Department, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
  - Science-Technology Information Center, 1970-1973 (Box 5)
  - Space Administrator, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1974-1977 (Box 5)
  - SHEV, Finance Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - State Librarian, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Student Affairs, Vice-President for, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Student Health, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
  - Treasurer, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Treasurer, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - University Comptroller, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - University Bicentennial Planning Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 5)
  - University Development Steering Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - University History Officer, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
  - University Police Department, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - University Press, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - University Printing Office, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
  - University Senate, 1971-1976, n. d. (Box 5)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
  - Visiting Scholars Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - WTJU, 1967-1971 (Box 5)
- Vice-President for Business and Finance 1977-1978
  - Alumni Association, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Board of Trustees, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Architecture, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Art, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Associate Provost for Research, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Athletics, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Birdwood, 1909, 1966-1970, 1971-1976, 2 folders. (Box 5)
  - Blue Ridge Sanatorium, 1977-1978, 3 folders. (Box 5)
  - Board of Visitors, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Board of Visitors, Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Board of Visitors, Finance Committee, 1977 June-1978 June, 4 folders. (Box 5)
  - Board of Visitors, Health Sciences Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Board of Visitors, Student Affairs and Athletics Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Budget, Biennium 1978-1980, 1975-1978 (Box 6)
  - Budget Director, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Building Program, Blue Ridge Sanatorium, 1977 February-October (Box 6)
  - Business and Auxiliary Services, Director of, 1977 February-1978 May, 3 folders. (Box 6)
  - Business and Finance, Vice-President for, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Clinch Valley College, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate School of Business Administration, 1976-1978 (Box 6)
  - Comptroller, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Computing Activities, Region II, 1976-1978 (Box 6)
  - Comptroller for Medical Affairs, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education, School of, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Council of the President, State Council of Higher Education, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Council of State Senior Business Officers, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Division of Personnel, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Division of the Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - EACUBO, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Endowment Funds, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Endowment Funds (Consolidated), 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Endowment Funds (Eminent Scholars), 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, School of, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Faculty Salaries [American Association of University Professors], 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Financial Reports, U. Va., 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Food Services, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Governor, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Health Sciences, Vice-President, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Hospital, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Housing Office, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Internal Audit Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Law, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Legal Advisor, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - McIntire School of Commerce, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Medicine, School of, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Medical Center, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Department of, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs, 1974-1978 (Box 6)
  - Miller, Burkett White Center, Council of, 1976-1978 (Box 6)
  - Mortgage Loans, Approved Applications, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - NACUBO, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Parking and Transit, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Patent Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Personnel Office, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - President, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Property, Miscellaneous, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
  - Provost, 1971-1978 (Box 7)
  - Purchasing Agent, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Purchases and Supply, Department of, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
  - Research Policy Council, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - SCHEV, Finance Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Student Affairs, Vice-President for, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Treasurer, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - University Comptroller, 1976-1978 (Box 7)
  - University Printing Office, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - University Relations, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
- Vice President for Business and Finance 1978-1979
  - Accounting Services, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Administration and Finance, Secretary of, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Admissions, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Alumni Board of Trustees, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1978-1979, 2 folders. (Box 7)
  - Architecture, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Associate Provost for Research, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Astronomy, 1976-1979 (Box 7)
  - Athletic Panel, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Athletics, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Attorney General, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Audits, Director of (Search Committee), 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Audit (HEW), 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Audit (Price, Waterhouse and Company), 1977, 2 folders. (Box 7)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Biology, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - 1980-1982 Biennial Budget Documents, File II, 1978-1979, 2 folders. (Box 7)
  - Blue Ridge Sanatorium, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Board of Visitors, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Board of Visitors, Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Board of Visitors, Finance Committee, 1978-1979, 2 folders. (Box 8)
  - Board of Visitors, Health Sciences Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Board of Visitors, Student Affairs and Athletics Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Budget Director, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Business and Finance, Vice-President for, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Business Operations, Director of, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Cambridge Associates, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Cavalier Daily, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Center for Advanced Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Clinch Valley College, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate School of Business Administration, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - College, Dean of, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Comptroller, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Comptroller for Medical Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Computing Activities- Region II, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education, School of, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Council of State Senior Business Officers, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Council of the President, State Council of Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Development, Vice-President for, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Division of Personnel and Training, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - EACUBO, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - EEOOR Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1978-1979, 2 folders. (Box 8)
  - Endowment Funds, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Endowment Fund, Eminent Scholars, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Endowment Funds, Proxy Voting, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, School of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Environmental Sciences, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Executive Vice-President, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Dean of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Food Services, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - General Services, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Governor, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Health Affairs, Vice-President of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Heritage Repertory Theatre, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Hospital, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Housing Office, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Institutional Analysis Office, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Internal Auditor, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Law, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Legal Advisor, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Library, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - McIntire School of Commerce, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Medical Faculty Salary Plan (Clinicians), 1959-1979 (Box 9)
  - Medicine, School of, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Miller, Burkett Center for Public Affairs, 1978-1979, 2 folders. (Box 9)
  - Mortgage Loans, Approved Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Mortgage Loans, Faculty, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - NACUBO, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Parking and Transit, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Patent Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Personnel Office, 1978-1979, 3 folders. (Box 10)
  - Planning and Budget, Division of, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - President, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Price, Waterhouse and Company, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Provost, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Purchasing Agent, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Registrar, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Religious Studies, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - RLES, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - RLES Audit, 1977-1979 (Box 10)
  - Research Policy Council, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Residential Housing and Subsidiary Services, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Retirement Plans VSRS, TIAA, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - SCHEV, Finance Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Sholarships and Fellowships, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs, Vice-President for, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Student Council, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Student Loan Program, National Defense, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Summer Quarter, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Treasurer, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - University Comptroller, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - University Senate, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
- Vice-President for Business and Finance, 1979-1980
  - Admissions, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Association, 1977, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Board of Trustees, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1980, 3 folders. (Box 10)
  - Assistant Executive Vice President, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Associate Provost for Research, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Athletics, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Blue Ridge Sanatorium, 1977, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Audit Committee, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Finance Committee, 1980, 6 folders. (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Health Affairs Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Student Affairs and Athletics Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Budget, Biennium 1980-1981, 1979, 2 folders. (Box 11)
  - Budget, Director of, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Maintenance, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Business and Finance, Vice-President for, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Business Operations, Director of, 1979-1980, 2 folders. (Box 11)
  - Cambridge Associates, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - The Cavalier Daily, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate School of Business Administration, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - College, Dean of, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Colonnade Club, 1974-1980 (Box 11)
  - Committees, Administrative, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Comptroller for Medical Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Computer Center, Region II, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Continuing Education, School of, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Development, Vice-President for, 1978-1980 (Box 11)
  - EACUBO, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - EACUBO, Program Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Endowment Fund, Consolidated, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Endowment Fund, Eminent Scholars, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Endowment Fund, Proxy Voting, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Endowment Funds, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Endowment Funds, Investment Manager, Selection of, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Energy Conservation Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, School of, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs, Office of, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Executive Vice-President, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Dean of, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Salaries (American Association of University Professors), 1978-1979 (Box 12)
  - Fiscal Operations, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Food Services, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Graduate Studies, Dean of, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
  - Health Affairs, Vice-President for, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Health Services Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Health Services Foundation, Work Papers, 1979-1980, 2 folders. (Box 12)